

Davide Beretta

Web developer

Hi! My name is Davide and I'm a junior Web Developer based in Bergamo, Italy.

After 5 years in Administration and Controlling department, in 2017, I decided to take a turn in my career to follow something I'm really passionate about - web development. I have been studying online with the Odin Project, starting from the basics and then focusing on Ruby on Rails. At the moment, I'm looking for job opportunities in companies to enhance my professional experience but I'm also considering freelance jobs, so if you have a project to develop, get in touch!

Address

24047, Treviglio, BG, Italy

Date of birth 11 / 01 / 1987

Phone

+39 366 53 68 933

Email

contact@davideberetta.eu

Web

www.davideberetta.eu

Github

https://github.com/Isashi



Skills

HTML/CSS

Rails

Ruby

Bootstrap

Javascript



Languages

Italian

English

French

Spanish



Experience

2017 - 2018

.8

Junior Web developer

Developer of static websites, landing pages and

web applications.

Freelance

2014 - 2017

Treasury Analyst /
Industrial Controller

Exide Technologies

Treasury dpt: responsible for Cash Flow

Forecast, bank payments, cheques

management

Controlling dpt: controller for the company Industrial Business (P&L, warehouses, inventory, customer profitability)

2013 - 2014

Art Cosmetics

Controller

Responsible for industrial cost analysis, customers profitability margin, annual competitors benchmark, logistics analysis



Education

2017

The Odin Project

Online web development course (HTML, CSS, Ruby, Rails, Javascript, Bootstrap, Jquery)

2009 - 2011

Università degli Studi di Bergamo

Management, Finance and International

Business (110L/110)

2006 - 2009

Università degli Studi di Bergamo

Economics and Business Administration

(105/110)



Hobbies

- Reading

- Hiking

- Sketching

- Cooking

- Travelling